School of Dental Medicine Records UA020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Dental Medicine Records
1868 -- 2020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Dental Medicine
Miller, Russell E.
UA020
31.32 Linear Feet 30 boxes and 5 oversize folders.
23 Volumes
44 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into six series: Subject files; Minutes; Photographs, artifacts, and videos; Student theses, dissertations, papers; additional accessions; and 2020 accessions.
Custodial History
Originally the collection contained material gathered by Russell Miller in preparation for writing his two volume history of Tufts, Light on the Hill. It includes subject files from or about the Dental School, Senior Dental Essays (Peridontia Papers) and Junior Dental Essays (Operative Dental Essays). This material was arranged by subject and no attempt has been made to recreate original order. Material relating to administering the collection was removed to the documentation files of the collection in the archives.
New additions were made recently.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes artifacts, brochures, correspondence, meeting minutes, photographs, videos, student papers and theses, and subject files. Significant topics addressed in this collection include the history of the Tufts School of Dental Medicine, as well as the activities of its administrative officials, faculty members, and students.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts University School of Dental Medicine was established in 1868 as Boston Dental College. It was incorporated into Tufts College in 1899. Although founded as a school to educate students from New England, today Tufts is renowned throughout the United States and the world as a center for academic and clinical excellence. Tufts boasts over 6,900 alumni composed of individuals from all fifty states and thirty-nine countries. The majority of the alumni outside of the USA have completed an Advanced Education Certificate program. Students receive a comprehensive education emphasizing the importance of didactic coursework, clinical experience, and practice management that prepares them to enter the work force as confident, proficient clinicians.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Curriculum and Instruction -- Student Work; Curriculum and Instruction -- Faculty; Advancement; Administration and Governance -- Accreditation; Curriculum and Instruction
- Subject files, 1868 -- 1994; UA020.001; 2.75 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains reports, correspondence, brochures, and other materials related to the School of Dental Medicine.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Accreditation: Postdoctoral programs, 1969; UA020.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Accreditation: D.M.D. Program, 1970; UA020.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Advanced Education Programs, 1977; UA020.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Curriculum, 1977; UA020.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Survey Manual D.M.D. Program, 1977; UA020.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Self-Study Manual, 1985; UA020.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Self-Study Manual, 1994; UA020.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - American Academy of the History of Dentistry Bulletin - Tufts Centennial Issue, 1970; UA020.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
    Vol. 18 no. 1 of the Bulletin of the History of Dentistry.
  - Boston Dental College 1898-1899, correspondence and [ownership transfer certificates], 1868 -- 1900; UA020.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
    Certificate filed with Corporations Division describing the transfer of ownership of the Boston Dental College to Tufts College was not part of the original collection but is similar to the internal certificate from the Boston Dental College. Certificate document title is unknown.
  - Boston Dental College Fraternities, 1896; UA020.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Boston Dental College Announcements, 1879 -- 1894; UA020.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Boston Dental School announcements & by-laws, 1886 -- 1900; UA020.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Biodental Engineering Research, 1970; UA020.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Boston School of Dental Nursing, 1961 -- 1962; UA020.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Clippings, 1937 -- 1971; UA020.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Dental School Correspondence, 1951 -- 1961; UA020.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Dental School Correspondence, 1962 -- 1964; UA020.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Dental School Correspondence (Office of the Dean), 1960 -- 1991; UA020.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - [Letter of final settlement between Tufts College and Boston Dental College], 1903; UA020.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, 1965; UA020.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Curriculum, 1962 -- 1974; UA020.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Curriculum, Laboratory Workbooks, 1970; UA020.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Curriculum, Workbook, 1970; UA020.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Data Processing Feasibility Study, 1965; UA020.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Data Assistant Program, 1964 -- 1969; UA020.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Dental Equipment Fund, 1930 -- 1952; UA020.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, Pre-dental/Pre-medical, 1916 -- 1929; UA020.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Faculty-Staff, 1959 -- 1991; UA020.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, Pre-dental/Pre-medical, 1916 -- 1929; UA020.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Federal Board of Vocational Education, 1918 -- 1920; UA020.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Forsyth School, 1970; UA020.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Fund Raising-Steering Committee, 1966 -- 1967; UA020.001.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Fund Raising-Steering Committee, 1967; UA020.001.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Grant Application, 1965; UA020.001.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Grant Application, 1967; UA020.001.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Grant Application, 1968; UA020.001.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Occlusion Research Program, 1975; UA020.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - [Program Evaluation], 1967; UA020.001.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Workshop: Blueprint for the Future, 1965; UA020.001.010.00003 (Box 10)
- Minutes, 1878 -- 1959; UA020.002; 3.6 Linear Feet
  This series contains three bound volumes of meeting minutes from the Board of Trustees of the Boston Dental College, the Faculty of the Tufts Dental School, and the Faculty of the Tufts Dental School Administrative Committee.
  This series has no arrangement.
  - Board of Trustees, Boston Dental College, 1878-01-02 -- 1902-09-24; UA020.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Faculty Records, 1914-10-16 -- 1958-02-12; UA020.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Administrative Committee Records, 1914-09-03 -- 1959-06-02; UA020.002.008.00001 (Box 8)
- Photographs, artifacts, and videos, 1910 -- 2020; UA020.003; 21.17 Linear Feet 16 oversized boxes and oversized folders in a map case.; 44 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains photographs, artifacts, and videos related to the School of Dental Medicine.
  - Two Unidentified Dental Students Working on Dentures, 1930; UA020.003.001.00001 (Box 1)
    The image is attached to "Tufts College - A Seat of Learning in New England" which has a description of the Tufts College Dental Clinic.
  - Tufts Dental School Students and Patients in the Dental Clinic, 1931; UA020.003.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Dental School Photos, 1928 -- 1943; UA020.003.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Dental School Photos, 1965 -- 1973; UA020.003.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Dental School Photos, 1973; UA020.003.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Dental School Photos, 1973; UA020.003.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Psi Omega Fraternity, 1929; UA020.003.001.00007 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    Belonged to Hurant Sherman Santoian, donated by his daughter Barbara Tomasian.
  - Psi Omega Fraternity certificate, 1930; UA020.003.001.00008 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
  - School of Dental Medicine diploma, 1930; UA020.003.001.00009 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
  - Board of Dental Examiners certificate, 1930; UA020.003.001.00010 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
  - Dental Commencement booklet, 1930; UA020.003.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Joseph E. Primack D'42 photographs and ephemera, 1938 -- 1992; UA020.003.001.00012 (Box 1)
    One photo of Primack as student with microscope; two photos of Primack providing dental care to Reevan Levine on 1941-02-28, photos taken by Ralph Slate; three photos from reunion in 1992 and presentation of acknowledgment of 50 years of service; copy of Class of 1942 photograph; Petition for the suspension of classes on the Friday following Thanksgiving, 1938. Donated by Philip Primack.
  - School of Dental Medicine diploma, 1918; UA020.003.001.00013 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    Diploma of Joseph Weener. Donated by Lucille Janis Weener, his daughter-in-law.
  - School of Dental Medicine diploma and Board Certification, 1919; UA020.003.001.00014 (Box Large Map Case 2 Drawer 6)
    Diploma of William Francis Reid. Donated by Ginger Reid.
  - School of Dental Medicine clock, 1980 -- 1995; UA020.003.002.00001 (Box 2)
    Belonged to Joseph E. Primack D'42 and donated by his son Philip Primack.
  - Tufts Dental Medicine club mug, 1980 -- 1995; UA020.003.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Dental school operatory, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00005 (Box Shared 83)
    Dental students; Students; People; School of Dental Medicine, records; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dental school operatory, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00006 (Box Shared 83)
  - Francis W. Sargent at groundbreaking of dental school, 1970; UA020.003.DO.00007 (Box Shared 43)
    Events; People; School of Dental Medicine, records; Sargent, Francis W.; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dental school exterior, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00008 (Box Shared 83)
    Buildings; Academic; Administrative; People; School of Dental Medicine, records; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dental School building on Huntington Ave., 1910; UA020.003.DO.00009
    Illustration in Light on the Hill, p.245
    Buildings; Academic; Administrative; School of Dental Medicine, records; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dental school professor, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00010 (Box Shared 43)
    Faculty; People; School of Dental Medicine, records; School of Dental Medicine
  - Washington and Kneeland Street, Dental school exterior, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00024 (Box Shared 142)
  - Dental school lobby, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00025 (Box Shared 142)
  - Dental School during construction, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00026
    Explorer 73 pp. 42-43
  - Theater District/Chinatown, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00027
    Explorer 73 p. 37
    Buildings; School of Dental Medicine, records; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dental School construction, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00028
    First half of photograph of building exterior; Explorer 73 p.42
  - Dental School construction, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00029
    Second half of photograph of building exterior; Explorer 73 p. 43
  - Dental School construction, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00030
    View of Chinatown #1
  - Dental School construction, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00031
    Two construction workers; Explorer 73 p. 61
  - Horizontal crane against Dental School construction, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00032
    Explorer 73 p. 60
  - Scaffolding of Dental School building, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00033
    Academic; Administrative; Buildings; School of Dental Medicine, records; School of Dental Medicine
  - Horizontal crane on street, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00034
    Dental School construction; Explorer 73 p. 60
  - Dental School construction, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00035
    View of Chinatown #2
  - Dental School groundbreaking, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00036
    Events; Buildings; Academic; Administrative; People; School of Dental Medicine, records; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dental School groundbreaking, 1973; UA020.003.DO.00037
    Events; Buildings; Academic; Administrative; People; School of Dental Medicine, records; Hallowell, Burton Crosby; School of Dental Medicine
  - Harrison Ave., 1973; UA020.003.DO.00038
    Explorer 73 p. 36
    --School of Dental Medicine, records; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dr. Max H. Jacobs in clinic with students, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01728; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Dr. Max H. Jacobs was Clinical Professor of Oral Surgery.
    Dental students; Jacobs, Max H.; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dental students in dental classroom, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01729; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Students identified as: E. Steven Pickman, James H. O'Connor, Robert S. Potter.
    Dental students; Laboratories; School of Dental Medicine
  - J. Murray Gavel, 1963; UA020.003.DO.01730; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Photo labeled "J. Murray Gavel, Acting Dean, 1962-63."
    Portraits; Paintings; College administrators; Gavel, J. Murray; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dental class, preclinical technic, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01731; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
  - Reception desk in dental clinic, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01732; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    People; Receptionists; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dr. Dmitri A. Afonsky, Director of Graduate Studies, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01733; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Portraits; Afonsky, Dmitri A.; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dental library, 1965; UA020.003.DO.01734; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Libraries; Dental students; Paintings; Carmichael, Leonard; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dental students talking in front of annoucement board, 1965; UA020.003.DO.01735; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Dental students; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dr. Frederic R. Shiere and asscociates, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01736; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Caption reads: "Center: Dr. Frederic R. Shiere, Director of the Cleft Palate Institute."
    Shiere, Frederick R.; School of Dental Medicine
  - Tufts Dental Clinic, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01737; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Dentistry; Dentists; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dr. Gerald Shklar, Chairman of Department of Oral Pathology, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01738; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Professors; Offices; Shklar, Dr. Gerald; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dental class in preclinical technic, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01739; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
  - Dr. Manly and Miss Cranick, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01740; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Professors; Dental students; Manly, R.S.; School of Dental Medicine
  - Demonstration case in Tufts Dental Clinic, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01741; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Dentistry; Patients; Dentists; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dr. Peter N. Kondon, clinical instructor in partial denture prosthesis, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01742; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Caption reads: "Center: Dr. Peter N. Kondon, Clinical Instructor in Partial Denture Prosthesis."
    Professors; Dentistry; Dental students; School of Dental Medicine
  - Lecture employing closed circuit television, 1965; UA020.003.DO.01743; Magna Fillm Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Dental students; Lectures or lecturing; Closed-circuit television; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dr. George A. Wolf, Jr., 1961; UA020.003.DO.01744 (Box Shared 114)
    College administrators; Wolf, George A., Jr.; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dr. Irving Glickman demonstrates closed-circuit television to Tufts alumni, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01745 (Box Shared 114)
    Original caption reads: "Dr. Irving Glickman, Professor of Oral Pathology, demonstrates closed-circuit television to over 500 Tufts Alumni."
    Dentistry; Closed-circuit television; Glickman, Irving; School of Dental Medicine
  - Dr. Max Jacobs presents a clinic on closed-circuit television to Tufts alumni, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01746 (Box Shared 114)
    Original caption reads: "Dr. Max Jacobs, right, Prof. of Oral Surgery, presents a clinic on closed circuit television to Tufts Alumni."
    Professors; Closed-circuit television; Jacobs, Max H.; School of Dental Medicine
  - Basil L. Henriques, Associate Professor of Dental Science, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01747; Magna Fillm Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Professors; Portraits; Henriques, Basil L.; School of Dental Medicine
  - Mrs. Cynthia Carter, nurse in oral surgery, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01750; Magna Fillm Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Nurses; Women; Carter, Cynthia; School of Dental Medicine
  - R.S. Manly, Director of Research, and Esther Granick, Research Technician, 1960; UA020.003.DO.01751; Magna Film Productions (Box Shared 114)
    Original caption reads: "Dr. R.S. Manly, Director of Research, and helper, Esther Granick, Research Technician."
    People; Manly, R.S.; Granick, Esther; School of Dental Medicine
  - School of Dental Medicine 150th Anniversary Gala, 2018-09-28; UA020.003.DO.01752; 1 Digital Object(s); 600 Megabytes
    Video of the School of Dental Medicine's 150th Anniversary Gala on September 28, 2018 at the Museum of Science in Boston, MA. Program speakers included Richard Valachovic, President and CEO of ADEA; Dean Huw Thomas; President Anthony Monaco; and Swaitha Maripuri, D19.
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Donated by University Advancement Special Events on behalf of TUSDM, 2018, accession UA-2019-043.
  - Dental School class picture, circa 1900s; UA020.000138; 1 Digital Object(s); 66.4 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Dental School class picture, 1900; UA020.000139; 1 Digital Object(s); 52.6 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Dental School class picture, 1904; UA020.000140; 1 Digital Object(s); 121 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Dental School class picture, 1907; UA020.000141; 1 Digital Object(s); 202 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Dental School class picture, 1909; UA020.000142; 1 Digital Object(s); 157 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Dental School class picture, 1910; UA020.000143; 1 Digital Object(s); 214 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Reunion Dental School class picture, 1910; UA020.000144; 1 Digital Object(s); 45.3 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Dental School class picture, 1912; UA020.000145; 1 Digital Object(s); 150 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Dental School class picture, 1913; UA020.000146; 1 Digital Object(s); 228 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Dental School class picture, 1914; UA020.000147; 1 Digital Object(s); 171 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Dental School class picture, 1915; UA020.000148; 1 Digital Object(s); 180 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Dental School class picture, 1916; UA020.000149; 1 Digital Object(s); 120 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Dental School class picture, 1917; UA020.000150; 1 Digital Object(s); 114 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Dental School class picture, 1918; UA020.000151 (Object 14)
  - Dental School class picture, 1923; UA020.000152; 1 Digital Object(s); 155 Megabytes (Object 15)
  - Dental School class picture, 1924; UA020.000153; 1 Digital Object(s); 173 Megabytes (Object 16)
  - Dental School class picture, 1927; UA020.000154; 1 Digital Object(s); 167 Megabytes (Box 3)
  - Dental School class picture, 1928; UA020.000155; 1 Digital Object(s); 31.9 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Dental School class picture, 1931; UA020.000156; 1 Digital Object(s); 161 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1932; UA020.000157; 1 Digital Object(s); 168 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1934; UA020.000158; 1 Digital Object(s); 184 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1935; UA020.000159; 1 Digital Object(s); 181 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1936; UA020.000160; 1 Digital Object(s); 162 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1937; UA020.000161; 1 Digital Object(s); 147 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1940; UA020.000162; 1 Digital Object(s); 211 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1941; UA020.000163; 1 Digital Object(s); 198 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Dental School class picture, 1942; UA020.000164; 1 Digital Object(s); 171 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Dental School class picture, 1942; UA020.000165; 1 Digital Object(s); 50.3 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1943; UA020.000166; 1 Digital Object(s); 175 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1944; UA020.000167; 1 Digital Object(s); 179 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1945; UA020.000168; 1 Digital Object(s); 174 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1946; UA020.000169; 1 Digital Object(s); 172 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1947; UA020.000170; 1 Digital Object(s); 139 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1948; UA020.000171; 1 Digital Object(s); 158 Megabytes (Box 4)
  - Dental School class picture, 1950; UA020.000172; 1 Digital Object(s); 133 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1951; UA020.000173; 1 Digital Object(s); 159 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1952; UA020.000174; 1 Digital Object(s); 145 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1954; UA020.000175; 1 Digital Object(s); 154 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1955; UA020.000176; 1 Digital Object(s); 183 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1956; UA020.000177; 1 Digital Object(s); 163 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1957; UA020.000178; 1 Digital Object(s); 141 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1958; UA020.000179; 1 Digital Object(s); 163 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1959; UA020.000180; 1 Digital Object(s); 131 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1960; UA020.000181; 1 Digital Object(s); 144 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1961; UA020.000182; 1 Digital Object(s); 135 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1962; UA020.000183; 1 Digital Object(s); 145 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1963; UA020.000184; 1 Digital Object(s); 123 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1964; UA020.000185; 1 Digital Object(s); 146 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1965; UA020.000186; 1 Digital Object(s); 148 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1966; UA020.000187; 1 Digital Object(s); 144 Megabytes (Box 5)
  - Dental School class picture, 1973; UA020.000188; 1 Digital Object(s); 193 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Dental School class picture, 1975; UA020.000189; 1 Digital Object(s); 187 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Dental School class picture 1975A, UA020.000190; 1 Digital Object(s); 193 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Dental School class picture, 1976; UA020.000191; 1 Digital Object(s); 147 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Dental School class picture, 1977; UA020.000192; 1 Digital Object(s); 121 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Dental School class picture, 1978; UA020.000193; 1 Digital Object(s); 220 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Dental School class picture, 1979; UA020.000194; 1 Digital Object(s); 121 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1979; UA020.000195; 1 Digital Object(s); 82.1 Megabytes (Box 6)
  - Dental School class picture, 1980; UA020.000196; 1 Digital Object(s); 136 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1980; UA020.000197; 1 Digital Object(s); 58.3 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School class picture, 1981; UA020.000198; 1 Digital Object(s); 138 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1981; UA020.000199; 1 Digital Object(s); 58.6 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School class picture, 1982; UA020.000200; 1 Digital Object(s); 133 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1982; UA020.000201; 1 Digital Object(s); 56.7 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School class picture, 1983; UA020.000202; 1 Digital Object(s); 134 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1983; UA020.000203; 1 Digital Object(s); 103 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1984; UA020.000204; 1 Digital Object(s); 86.7 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School class picture, 1985; UA020.000205; 1 Digital Object(s); 128 Megabytes (Box 7)
  - Dental School International class picture, 1985; UA020.000206; 1 Digital Object(s); 105 Megabytes (Box 7)